YAUHENIYA ZIALENKA

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER



EDUCATION

Front-End intern

Eventizer StartUp September, 2022 - now

Front-end/JS Course

The Rolling Scopes School June, 2022 -September, 2023

React Course

The Rolling Scopes School October, 2023 -

January, 2024

Family physician

Belarusian State Medical University 2013 - 2019

Windows,

MacOS

SPA

EXPERIENCE

Junior Front-end developer 2022-now

freelance

Doctor 2019-2022

Hospital, MInsk

Nurse 2018-2019

Oncology Center, Minsk

Nurse 2017-2018

Hospital, MInsk

EXPERTISE

Html5, CSS3, React, Scss React Hooks

JavaScript, Next.js git, Github

TypeScript react-router-don

react-router-dom, npm, yarn react-hook-form

Fetch React Context

OOP Grid, FlexBox Redux, RTK

firebase

HTTP,HTTPS Webpack Responsive WEB

REST API Vite design

Jest, Vitest ESlint Figma

eCommerce

PROFILE

My name is Evgenia.

I am 27 years old. I dedicated 9 years to medicine and decided to change my field of activity. I graduated from Front-end and React courses at The Rolling Scopes School.

I easily assimilate information, learn quickly, can switch from one task to another easily, and enjoy handling non-standard situations. I am stress-resistant, calm, and ready to take action.

I am looking for a job or internship in Front-end development. I am interested in reactive technologies, especially React.

LANGUAGES

Russian, English - B2, French - B1 Polish(beginner)

PROJECTS

https://evgueniazet.github.io/#/

https://commandor05-onlinestore.netlify.app/

https://graphiql-app-eoby.vercel.app/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/rs-css/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/shelter/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/songbird/

https://evgueniazet.github.io/cssBayan/cssBayan/index.html

CONTACTS

email: yauheniyazialenka@gmail.com phone: +375 25 773 74 30, +48 511 250 189 github: https://github.com/evgueniazet